sescoops.com 2018-09-29

# Privacy Policy - SEScoops

SEScoops.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site:

**Information Automatically Logged**  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

**Cookies**  
Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly, and, if you are a member, to keep you logged in.

**Advertisers**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [**click here**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

**Contests**  
We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like email address). Contact information from the contests is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. SEScoops.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Data Quality/Access**  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: You can send email to [**[email  protected]**](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#70131f1e0411130430031503131f1f00035e131f1d)

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can reach us at [ **[email  protected]**](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#ed8e8283998c8e99ad9e889e8e82829d9ec38e8280)

**Exponential** :  
Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
